Bruce A. Morrison Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Bruce A. Morrison Papers.
undated, 1980-2000.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Morrison, Bruce A.
127 linear feet.
Bruce Morrison served as a member of Congress from Connecticut's third district from 1983-1991.
MSS19910021
Biography
Bruce Morrison is Chairman of the Morrison Public Affairs Group (MPAG), which he founded in 2001 to conduct and supervise a broad practice involving strategic advice and representation for both domestic and international clients. His work involves advocacy in both Congress and the Executive branch, as well as building alliances within the private sector. His areas of expertise include immigration policy, financial services, housing finance, privacy, and intellectual property. Prior to founding MPAG, he was Vice Chairman of the Washington office of GPC International.
From 1995 to 2000, Mr. Morrison served as Chairman of the Federal Housing Finance Board, an independent agency regulating the twelve Federal Home Loan Banks, a wholesale banking system with assets in excess of $600 billion. In this role, he developed and implemented a far-reaching strategy to modernize the business of the Banks.
His work included the successful advocacy of the passage of the Federal Home Loan Bank Modernization Act of 1999, a bi-partisan effort which provided for new powers for the Banks, devolution of management, and a modern risk-based capital structure. Mr. Morrison provided the Banks with new business opportunities in housing finance and economic development through pilot programs and regulatory innovations. He spearheaded the agency through an aggressive regulatory agenda in the first six months of 2000 to implement the statutory changes and institutionalize the expanded authority of the Banks.
From 1983 to 1991, Mr. Morrison represented the Third District of Connecticut (New Haven) in the U.S. House of Representatives. He served on the Banking Committee, playing a leadership role in financial services oversight, housing and housing finance, and U.S. policy regarding the World Bank, the IMF, and the LDC debt crisis.
He also served on the Judiciary Committee, where he specialized in intellectual property issues, bankruptcy law, consumer protection policy, including privacy, and immigration. As chairman of the Immigration Subcommittee, he led the passage of the Immigration Act of 1990, a comprehensive reform, which included expanded admission of skilled workers. He also served on the committees on Veterans Affairs and the District of Columbia, and on the Select Committee on Children, Youth and Families.
Mr. Morrison was the Democratic candidate for Governor of Connecticut in 1990. From 1991 to 1995, he was a partner in the law firm of Morrison & Swaine, specializing in immigration and international trade and investment. In 1992 and 1996, he was Co-Chairman of Irish- Americans for Clinton-Gore, and served throughout the Clinton Administration as an advisor and intermediary in the Irish peace process. From 1992 to 1995, he was a member of the U.S. Commission on Immigration Reform.
Mr. Morrison holds a bachelor's degree in chemistry from MIT and a master's degree in organic chemistry from the University of Illinois. He is a graduate of the Yale Law School.
Scope and Content
The Bruce Morrison Papers contain the office files of four legislative assistants to Mr. Morrison during his Congressional membership from 1983-1990, as well as constituent correspondence for the period. Additions to the collection document his activities through 2000, although this portion of the collection has not yet been processed.
Arrangement
The papers have been arranged in five series; two subsequent additions have not yet been integrated into the main body of the collection.
Series I: Legislative Assistant: Paul Drolet ( undated, 1982-1990 ) contains papers filed by the Senior Legislative Assistant to Bruce Morrison. Mr. Drolet's chief responsibilities were with the Banking and Judiciary Committees. The series in arranged in four subseries: Record Statements, Issues and Legislation, Banking and Finance, and Subject Files. Record Statements records the proceedings and debates of the 98th to 101st Congressional sessions, 1983-1989, with news clippings of the Congressional Record, along with summary statements by Morrison. Issues and Legislation, 1982-1990, includes materials on budget, defense, foreign affairs, as well as files on organizations such as Nationwide Insurance and the Federal Employee Union. Banking and Finance contains files on the Federal Savings & Loan Insurance Corporation bailout, as well as material on the subject of financial deregulation. Subject Files (1982-1990) includes information on campaign finance, credit access files, letters of testimony on banking regulations and the Connecticut credit crunch, Long Island Sound issues, and long term care. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series II: Legislative Assistant: Stuart Gaul (undated, 1980-1990) contains files concerning the Select Committee on Child, Youth, and Family Services, as well as information on environmental issues. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series III: Legislative Assistant: Nora Engel ( 1983-1989 ) contains information on issues reviewed by Nora Engel from 1983-1989. Issues included are the 1988 Drug Bill and the fatal accident which occurred during the construction of the L'Ambiance Plaza in Bridgeport, Connecticut. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series IV: Legislative Correspondent: P. Knight Elsberry (undated, 1982-1990) contains the files of one of the several staff members who wrote letters for Mr. Morrison and is divided into several subseries: Issues and Legislation (undated, 1982-1990), Robos Letters (1983-1990) and KB Letter Subject Headings (1983-1990). Included in these files is information on the Iroquois natural gas pipeline, Price-Anderson Insurance, and the U.S. Citizenship of tennis professional Ivan Lendl in 1987. Also included in this series are KB and Robos letters, which are computer printout format letters filed according to subject headings such as taxes, trade, animal rights, and foreign affairs. Some KB letters have been filed under a subject heading, whereas others are filed according to the KB Entry number. In addition, there are press clippings from 1987-1990 on Connecticut issues pertinent to Bruce Morrison and his office.
Series V: Legislative Correspondence ( undated, 1983-1990 ) contains mail received by Morrison's office from constituents. The series includes correspondence from individuals and representatives of business, as well as organized citizen response to issues and legislation. This series is arranged by year and month, from January 1983 through December 1990.
Series VI: 1994 Addition
Series VII: 2000 Addition ( 1982-2000 ) includes materials on Morrison's Congressional and Gubernatorial campaigns, activities pertaining to the Irish Peace Process, and his chairmanship of the Federal Housing Finance Board.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials from Connecticut's Congressional delegation. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Places:
United States--Politics and government--1981-1989.; United States--Politics and government--1989-1993.
Subjects:
Legislators--United States.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Press releases.; Videocassettes.; Audio cassettes.
Occupations:
Legislators.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The papers were donated to the University of Connecticut libraries by Bruce A. Morrison in December 1990. Additional materials were donated in 1994 and 2000.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Legislative Assistant: Paul Drolet undated, 1982-1990
  - Subseries A: Record Statements, 1983-1989
    - 98th Congress, 1983 (Box 1:, Folder 1-2)
    - 98th Congress, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 3-5)
    - 99th Congress: 1st session, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 6-7)
    - 99th Congress: 2nd session, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 8)
    - 100th Congress: 1st session, 1987 (Box 2:, Folder 9)
    - 100th Congress: 2nd session, 1988 (Box 2:, Folder 10)
    - 101st Congress: 1st session, 1989 (Box 2:, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Issues and Legislation, undated, 1982-1990
    - Budget Materials
      - Deferral reform: Panetta (Box 3:, Folder 12)
      - Freeze Amendment—H.R. 1872, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 13)
      - Deficit control, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder 14)
      - FY86 priority material, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder 15)
      - Enforcement, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 16)
    - Defense
      - Deferral issue, 1986-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 17)
      - Deferral case, 1986-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 18)
      - Sikorsky, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 19)
      - Spending materials, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 20)
      - FY90 defense, 1990 (Box 3:, Folder 21)
      - FY88 interior appropriation, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 22)
      - Levine-Biden foreign military sales bill, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder 23)
      - National Guard technicians, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 24)
      - Sikorsky-Bates Amendment, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Affairs
      - Neutrality Act, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 26)
      - Taping controversy, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 27)
    - Organizations
      - Home builders, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 28)
      - National Association of Retired & Veteran Railway Employees, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 29)
      - Labor Building Trade (Box 3:, Folder 30)
      - Nationwide Insurance, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder 31)
      - Federal Employee Unions, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 32)
      - Labor, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 33)
      - Realtors, 1983-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 34)
      - Teamsters—mailing list, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 35)
      - Union Leaders—mailing list, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 36)
    - General Files
      - Army Reserve—76th training division, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 37)
      - Banking Committee/Subcommittee bidding, 1986-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 38)
      - BAM bills—100th Congress, 1987-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 39)
      - Democrats 2000, 1988-1989 (Box 3:, Folder 40)
      - Economic data on declining income, 1986-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 41)
      - Bob Harp—refugee issue, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 42)
      - Financial management talk, 1988-1990 (Box 3:, Folder 43)
      - Federal acquisition regulations system, 1988-1989 (Box 3:, Folder 44)
      - KAL 007, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 45)
      - League of Conservation Voters, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 46)
      - Miscellaneous texts and memos, 1987-1990 (Box 3:, Folder 47)
      - Morrison mailing, 1984-1987 (Box 3:, Folder 48)
      - Natori-Yale, 1987-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 49)
      - Railroad retirement issues, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 50)
      - U.S. Savings rate information, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 51)
      - “The Morning After” by Peterson, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 52)
      - Paul Drolet: travel expenses, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 53)
      - Veterans Center Relocation Committee, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 54)
      - Veterans: POW/MIA, 1983-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 55)
      - Veterans WWI survey, 1983-1984 (Box 3:, Folder 56)
    - Housing
      - Appropriations Bill Amendement, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 57)
      - Amendment to Bartlett Liability, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 58)
      - Jim Cohen/Chris Niedermeier, 1986-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 59)
      - Committee to Activate a Patriotic Majority, 1984-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 60)
      - Continuing Resolution reform, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 61)
      - Caucus: rules/waiver, 1987-1988 (Box 4:, Folder 62)
      - Davis-Bacon Urban Development Action Grants, 1985-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 63)
      - William Greider, 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 64)
      - Homeless initiative, 1986-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 65)
      - H.R. #1 Housing Act, 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 66)
      - H.R. #1 (H.R. #4746 substitute), 1985-1986 (Box 4:, Folder 67)
      - Fair Market rents, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 68)
      - H.R. #1 mandatory meals, 1985-1986 (Box 4:, Folder 69)
      - Minimum wage, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 70)
      - MFJ restrictions: Bell Co., 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 71)
      - Rules: House Democratic caucus, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 72)
      - Rob Schwartz, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 73)
      - Stamps, 1985-1987 (Box 4:, Folder 74)
      - Temporary mortgage assistance payments, 1982-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 75)
      - V.A. medical benefits, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 76)
      - Textron Lycoming (Stratford plant), 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 77)
      - UDAG funding, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 78)
    - Judiciary
      - Asset forfeiture, 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 79)
      - Bankruptcy labor, 1983-1984 (Box 4:, Folder 80)
      - Cable materials, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 81)
      - Digital audio tapes, 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 82)
      - Equal Access to Justice Act, 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 83)
      - Fat wire, 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 84)
      - F.B.I. salary issues, 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 85)
      - Flag mark-up, 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 86)
      - Fairness Doctrine, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 87)
      - Multi-state tax issue, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 88)
      - Judiciary Committee: Federal Tort Claims Act Revision, 1985-1988 (Box 4:, Folder 89)
      - Bankruptcy: discharge of restitution orders, 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 90)
      - Rules of Procedure: 101st Congress, undated (Box 4:, Folder 91)
      - Cable copyright, 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 92)
      - Trademark issues, 1984-1989 (Box 4:, Folder 93)
      - Legal Services Corporation, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 94)
      - McCarran-Ferguson, 1989-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 95)
      - Muzzoli-Hubbard Research, 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 96)
      - Product liability, 1988-1989 (Box 4:, Folder 97-98)
      - Satellite issues, 1987-1988 (Box 4:, Folder 99)
      - Trademark revision, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 100)
    - Local Projects
      - Advanced composite products, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 101)
      - Amtrak—single track issue, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 102)
      - Shirley Buckley, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 103)
      - Charter Federal, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 104)
      - Combustion Engineering, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 105)
      - Connecticut Liquidity Investment, 1987-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 106)
      - Danbury Prison, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 107)
      - Federal Court issues, 1987-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 108)
      - First Federal Bank conversion, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 109)
      - Firefighter death benefit case, 1982-1987 (Box 5:, Folder 110)
      - Harp and Carrigan, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 111)
      - Alberta Jagoe, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 112)
      - Terrence F. Kehoe, 1986-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 113)
      - Local rail issues, 1985 (Box 5:, Folder 114)
      - Ed Marcus/Dmitrina Pravtcheva, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 115)
      - Nike missile site, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 116)
      - Pollard Prison issues, 1987-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 117)
      - Saab—highway bill, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 118)
      - Saab-Scania “Buy American”, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 119)
      - Saab-Scania, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 120)
      - Saab-Scania, 1983-1987 (Box 5:, Folder 121)
      - Sikorsky/Black Hawk, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 122)
      - Suburban Bankers, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 123)
      - Textron China Work, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 124)
      - VA Hospital—West Haven renovation, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 125)
      - VA Heart Unit, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 126)
      - Washington Homes Ltd., 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 127)
      - Woodview Apartments, 1987-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 128)
    - Office Administration
      - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 129)
      - Job Applications, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 130)
      - Job Descriptions, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
      - Staff assignment notices, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 132)
      - Staff salary issue, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 133)
      - Appropriation Committee campaign, 1986-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 134)
      - Appropriations Committee bid, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 135)
      - Bankruptcy—In Forms Pauperis, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 136)
      - Kennedy-Morrison Amendment, 1989-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 137)
    - Social Security/Pension
      - Railroad retirees, 1985-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 138)
      - Budget Committee, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 139)
      - Senior judges, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 140)
      - Marriage Penalty, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 141)
      - Tax Fair—L.A. Times, April 3, 1985 (Box 5:, Folder 142)
      - Attorney Fees, 1986-1987 (Box 5:, Folder 143)
      - Tax cuts, 1981 (Box 5:, Folder 144)
      - Tax expenditure material, 1983-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 145)
      - Taxation—underground economy, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 146)
      - Vesting requirements for private pension Plans, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 147)
    - Taxation
      - ARCO pricing/wind fall profits, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 148)
      - Life Insurance, 1985 (Box 5:, Folder 149)
      - Tax Reform/Retirement Policy, 1985-1986 (Box 5:, Folder 150)
      - Solid Waste disposal, undated (Box 5:, Folder 151)
    - Trade
      - Conversion file, 1985 (Box 6:, Folder 152)
      - Exchange rate and tax issues, 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 153)
      - Lumber, 1985 (Box 6:, Folder 154)
      - Protectionism, 1985 (Box 6:, Folder 155)
    - Transportation Issues
      - Amtrak Firemen, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 156)
      - Amtrak Transportation, 1985-1986 (Box 6:, Folder 157)
      - Import restrictions, 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 158)
      - Locomotive Engineer stress, 1985 (Box 6:, Folder 159)
      - Steel import restrictions, 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 160)
      - Truck Safety, 1983-1986 (Box 6:, Folder 161-162)
    - Unemployment
      - Agency contacts list, 1986-1989 (Box 6:, Folder 163)
      - Connecticut judges bill, 1987-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 164)
      - Morrison biographies, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 165)
      - Press list, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 166)
      - Research Publications, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 167)
      - Compensation system, undated (Box 6:, Folder 168)
      - Connecticut rates, 1983-1989 (Box 6:, Folder 169)
      - Zip code directories, undated (Box 6:, Folder 170)
  - Subseries C: Banking and Finance, undated, 1982-1989
    - Bank investment contracts, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 171)
    - Congressional Quarterly Bank Clips, 1982-1987 (Box 7:, Folder 172)
    - Dear Colleagues letters—copies, 1988 (Box 7:, Folder 173)
    - Democratic Organizational Caucus, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 174)
    - Democratic Caucus rules for the Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 175)
    - Directors and Officers liability issues, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 176)
    - Economic Development Act, 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 177)
    - Empire Bank issues, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 178)
    - Federal Debt Collection Bill, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 179)
    - Federal Savings & Loan Insurance Corp.: bail out, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 180)
    - Federal Savings & Loan Insurance Corp.: general, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 181)
    - Financial deregulation, 1986-1988 (Box 7:, Folder 182-185)
    - Fair debt collection practices, 1985 (Box 7:, Folder 186)
    - Goodwill Floor Amendment, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 187)
    - H.R. $10: Economic Development Administration, 1983 (Box 7:, Folder 188)
    - H.R. #1278/206 Amendment, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 189)
    - Morrison Amendment, undated (Box 7:, Folder 190)
    - Mortgage serving rights disclosure, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 191)
    - Offers/Counters, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 192)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Regulation, 1986-1987 (Box 7:, Folder 193)
    - Section #604 Amendment, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 194)
    - Securities industry restructuring, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 195)
  - Subseries D: Subject Files, undated, 1982-1990
    - ABC Daycare Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 196)
    - Accu-Rite, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 197)
    - Adoption, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 198)
    - Age Discrimination, 1986-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 199)
    - American Express, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 200)
    - Amtrak, 1986-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 201)
    - Animals, 1986-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 202)
    - Army Corps, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 203)
    - Asbestos, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 204)
    - Automakers, undated (Box 8:, Folder 205)
    - Baby M, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 206)
    - Bennett Pudlin's Estopple, 1986-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 207-208)
    - Dalton Brennan, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 209)
    - Bicentennial, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 210)
    - B.U. Law School Speech, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 211)
    - Campaign finance, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 212-216)
    - Census, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 217)
    - Child Care Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 218)
    - Collateral Estoppel, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 219)
    - Colt Strike, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 220)
    - Committee Assignments—101st Congress, 1988-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 221)
    - Connecticut Public Transportation, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 222)
    - Credit access files, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 223-228)
    - Letters of testimony: Bank regulations and CT credit crunch, 1988-1990 (Box 9:, Folder 229-232)
    - Day care bills: news clips, 1988 (Box 9:, Folder 233)
    - Dear Colleagues: approved, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 234-235)
    - Dear Colleagues: No, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 236)
    - Designer drugs, 1983-1986 (Box 9:, Folder 237)
    - Diagnostic labs/Medicare, 1985 (Box 9:, Folder 238)
    - Digital Audio Tapes, 1987 (Box 9:, Folder 239)
    - Home Audio Recording, 1982-1985 (Box 9:, Folder 240-241)
    - Nancy Johnson—day care, 1988 (Box 10:, Folder 242)
    - Judiciary copyright, 1983 (Box 10:, Folder 243)
    - Judiciary committee: audio royalty, 1983-1985 (Box 10:, Folder 244)
    - Light net, 1986-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 245)
    - Long Island Sound, 1985-1989 (Box 10:, Folder 246-250)
    - Long term care, 1986-1988 (Box 10:, Folder 251-254)
    - M-1 Tank, 1983-1984 (Box 10:, Folder 255)
    - Massport/Air access, 1988 (Box 10:, Folder 256)
    - Medical waste disposal, 1988 (Box 10:, Folder 257-258)
    - Milford and New Haven Harbors, 1983-1984 (Box 10:, Folder 259)
    - Military Batteries, 1986 (Box 10:, Folder 260)
    - Miscellaneous projects, 1988-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 261-263)
    - New England Counsel article, undated (Box 11:, Folder 264)
    - Norwalk/CDBG, 1987 (Box 11:, Folder 265)
    - Oliver Industries/luggage rack issue, 1986 (Box 11:, Folder 266)
    - Oysters, 1988 (Box 11:, Folder 267)
    - Program housing - Sect. 235, 1982-1985 (Box 11:, Folder 268-269)
    - Republican day care bill, 1988 (Box 11:, Folder 270)
    - Rust engineering, 1988 (Box 11:, Folder 271)
    - Saab-Scania/Madison, Wis. Bus purchase, 1988 (Box 11:, Folder 272)
    - Sewage treatment plant program, 1987-1988 (Box 11:, Folder 273)
    - Shipping bill, 1984-1988 (Box 11:, Folder 274)
    - Starter Sportwear, 1986-1987 (Box 11:, Folder 275)
    - Senate statement - Morrison, 1990 Jun 27 (Box 11:, Folder 276)
    - Senate statement - Morrison, 1991 Jul 16 (Box 11:, Folder 277)
    - Travel arrangements, 1990 (Box 11:, Folder 278)
    - Turbine Components, 1985 (Box 11:, Folder 279)
    - Witness list: Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, 1990 (Box 11:, Folder 280)
- Series II: Legislative Assistant: Stuart Gaul, undated, 1980-1990
  - Acid rain, 1985-1990 (Box 12:, Folder 281)
  - Acid rain: Canada, 1988 (Box 12:, Folder 282)
  - AIDS, 1986-1988 (Box 12:, Folder 283-285)
  - Air pollution, 1988-1989 (Box 12:, Folder 286)
  - Animals, 1989-1990 (Box 12:, Folder 287-288)
  - Airlines, 1986-1987 (Box 12:, Folder 289)
  - Air pollution, 1985-1986 (Box 12:, Folder 290)
  - Asbestos, 1988 (Box 12:, Folder 291)
  - Alaska: Wildlife refuge, 1987-1989 (Box 12:, Folder 292)
  - Archived releases, 1989-1990 (Box 12:, Folder 293)
  - Baby M, 1987 (Box 12:, Folder 294)
  - Blind, the, 1989 (Box 12:, Folder 295-296)
  - B&M Railroad property, 1987-1988 (Box 12:, Folder 297)
  - Brady Bill, 1988 (Box 12:, Folder 298)
  - Budget, 1991 (Box 12:, Folder 299-300)
  - Catastrophic care, 1987-1990 (Box 12:, Folder 300-302)
  - Catastrophic Care/Medicare, 1988-1989 (Box 13:, Folder 303)